

# **PROFILE**

My name is Karalis Georgios, and I was born in Thessaloniki on 12 September 1995. I graduated from the Department of Informatics in the Ionian University of Corfu. Coding is my passion. I have worked with numerous programming languages and frameworks, Python being the most preferable.

### CONTACT

PHONE: 00 30 6989060708

WEBSITE:

https://p13kara33.github.io

EMAIL:

Georgekaralis7@gmail.com

## **HOBBIES**

Football Sailing Boxing Chess Cooking

# KARALIS GEORGIOS

Developer

# **EDUCATION**

**Ionian University Department of Informatics** 2013 – 2019

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

**Eldry – Web Developer** July 2016- August 2016

**Diadrasi Taiganidou Pyton Developer** July 2018

**Bee Plan - Real Estate Agent**July 2018 – August 2019

Eldry – Project Manager July 2019 – October 2019

## **SKILLS**

